Guide to the Gerald Stern Papers, 1920s-2012 SC.2007.04
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Correspondence, 1950-2007; IV.
  - Lesser-Known Poets, 1954-2007; 8.
    - Garland, Max, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 90)
    - Garrett, Sidney, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 91)
    - Gibson, Reginald O'Hare (Box 20, Folder 92)
    - Gillan, Maria Mazziotti, 1991-2006 (Box 20, Folder 93)
    - Glasser, Elton, 1982-2005 (Box 20, Folder 94)
    - Godine, David, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 95)
    - Goedicke, Patricia, 1990-1994 (Box 20, Folder 96)
    - Goldberg, Barbara, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 97)
    - Goodman, Joanna, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 98)
    - Gordon, Jaimy, 1983-1990 (Box 20, Folder 99)
    - Grossman, Jeffrey (Box 20, Folder 100)
    - Grubin, Eve, 1999-2005 (Box 20, Folder 101)
    - Hall, James and Mary Ann, 1983-2005 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Hallgren, Sherri (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Hamilton, David, 1987-2001 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Harrison, Jeffrey, 1987-2002 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Hathaway, Kit (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Hendrie, Don, 1985-1987 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Hillringhouse, Mark, 1983-2005 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Hoffman, Daniel, 1978-2002 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Horwitz, Ellen, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Humes, Harry, 1981-2006 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Iddings, Kathleen, 1985-1999 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Ignatow, Rose, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Inez, Colette, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Irwin, Mark, 1983-2004 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Jackson, Allen M., 1992-1993 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Jackson, Major L., 1997 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Jackson, Richard, 1996-2005 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Johnson, Susan, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Joseph, Larry, 1987-2010 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Junkins, Donald, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Kamenetz, Rodger, 1997-2001 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Kaufman, Janet, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Kearney, Meg, 1994-1996 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Keelan, Claudia, 1994-2006 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Keys, Kerry Shawn, 1975-2005 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Kirby, David, 2006-2007 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Klappert, Peter, 1980-1987 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Kocher, Ruth Ellen (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Kray, Elizabeth, 1982-1983 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Kroll, Judy (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Lazard, Naomi, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Lazer, Hank, 1978-1985 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Lea, Sydney, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Lechey, Jim (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Levi, Jan Heller, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Levin, Lynn E., 1999-2009 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Levine, Mark (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Lieberman, Laurence, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Logghe, Joan, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Losch, Rita, 1973-2003 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Lovett, Jim (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Lowenfels, Walter (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - Ludvigson, Susan, 1988-1990 (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - Lusk, Daniel, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - Lynch, Alessandra, 1989-2003 (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - Malanga, Gerald, 1976-2004 (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - Marcus, Julia, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 47)
    - Marcus, Mort, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 48)
    - Marlis, Stefanie, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 49)
    - Marshall, Donald G., 1988 (Box 21, Folder 50)
    - Matthews, Sebastian, 2005-2006 (Box 21, Folder 51)
    - McConkey, Jim, 1982-2005 (Box 21, Folder 52)
    - McGrew, Bruce and Fox, 1987-1999 (Box 21, Folder 53)
    - McNair, Wesley, 1992-1998 (Box 21, Folder 54)
    - Meinke, Peter, 1990-2006 (Box 21, Folder 55)
    - Merriam, Eve, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 56)
    - Mezey, Robert, 1982-1993 (Box 21, Folder 57)
    - Miller, Bonnie, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 58)
    - Miller, Jane, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 59)
    - Mills, Ralph, 1978-1981 (Box 21, Folder 60)
    - Morling, Malena, 1998-2007 (Box 21, Folder 61)
    - Morris, Mary (Box 21, Folder 62)
    - Mort, Jo-Ann, 1976-1983 (Box 21, Folder 63)
    - Murray, Joan, 1981-2006 (Box 21, Folder 64)
    - Musial, Grzegorz, 1988-1993 (Box 21, Folder 65)
    - Myers, Neil, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 66)
    - Nameroff, Rochelle, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 67)
    - Nathanson, Roy, 1982-1992 (Box 21, Folder 68)
    - Nims, John F. (Box 21, Folder 69)
    - Nolach, Cecilia, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 70)
    - O'Connell, Richard, 1960-1974 (Box 21, Folder 71)
    - O'Hanian, Hunter, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 72)
    - Oresick, Peter, 1980-2007 (Box 21, Folder 73)
    - Orlen, Steve, 1984-1989 (Box 21, Folder 74)
    - Pace, Rosalind, 1978-1996 (Box 21, Folder 75)
    - Pacernick, Gary, 1980-2005 (Box 21, Folder 76)
    - Pankey, Eric (Box 21, Folder 77)
    - Pape, Greg, 1983-1992 (Box 21, Folder 78)
    - Parmet, Harriet, 1999-2001 (Box 21, Folder 79)
    - Peters, Robert, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 80)
    - Pettit, Michael, 1984-1988 (Box 21, Folder 81)
    - Petrosky, Tony, 1995-2002 (Box 21, Folder 82)
    - Piccione, Anthony, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 83)
    - Pillin, William, 1979-1981 (Box 21, Folder 84)
    - Pirro, Sam, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 85)
    - Piscal, Mike, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 86)
    - Plymell, Charles (Box 21, Folder 87)
    - Pollito, Elizabeth (Box 21, Folder 88)
    - Pranges, Marmie, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 89)
    - Rackner, Barry, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 90)
    - Raffel, Burton (Box 21, Folder 91)
    - Ragan, James, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 92)
    - Ramsey, Jerry, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 93)
    - Rawlings, Hunter, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 94)
    - Rawson, Eric, 1989-1997 (Box 21, Folder 95)
    - Rice, Stan, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 96)
    - Richards, Peter, 1994-2003 (Box 21, Folder 97)
    - Rigsbee, David, 1992-2006 (Box 21, Folder 98)
    - Robbins, Doren, 1994-2006 (Box 21, Folder 99)
    - Roffman, Rosaly, 1986-2005 (Box 21, Folder 100)
    - Rosen, Kenneth, 1987-2004 (Box 21, Folder 101)
    - Rosenberg, Liz, 1981-1995 (Box 21, Folder 102)
    - Ross, Ted, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 103)
    - Rudman, Mark, 1980-1991 (Box 21, Folder 104)
    - Salazar, Rachel, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Sandy, Stephen, 1988-2004 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Santos, Rod (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Schalm, Karin, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Setton, Ruth K., 1999-2005 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Shechner, Mark, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Shelton, Richard, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Shinder, Jason, 1980-2000 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Shomer, Enid, 1991-1993 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Shultz, Philip, 1981-2006 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Siedlecki, Peter A., 1977-1988 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Simms, Michael, 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Simpson, David (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Singer, Sean, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Sklarew, Myra (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Smith, David, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Smith, Harry, 1972-2004 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Soldofsky, Alan, 1981-2003 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Solomon, Mark (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Sonde, Susan, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Soniat, Katherine (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Southwick, Marcia, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Standing, Sue, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Stitt, Peter, 1995-1998 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Stricker, Meredith, 1988-2007 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Stryk, Lucien, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Sugarman, Yerra, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Surat, Michele, 2006-2007 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Swander, Mary, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Sward, Robert, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Swenson, Karen, 2001-2004 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Szyper, Adam, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Tagliabue, John, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Task, Sergei, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Terranova, Elaine, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Thayil, Jeet (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Tiger, Madeline J., 1988-2002 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Timpane, John, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Traxler, Patricia, 1994-1996 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Tsalka, Dan (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Turner, Alberta, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - Ullman, Leslie (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - Urdang, Constance, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 43)
    - Van Brunt, H.L. (Lloyd), 1974-2006 (Box 22, Folder 44)
    - Van Sluijs, Sharon M., 1987-2004 (Box 22, Folder 45)
    - Vollmer, Judith, 1997-2004 (Box 22, Folder 46)
    - Wagner, John (Box 22, Folder 47)
    - Waldorf, Peter, 2006 (Box 22, Folder 48)
    - Walker, David, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 49)
    - Walker, Scott, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 50)
    - Wallace, Naomi, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 51)
    - Wallace, Ron, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 52)
    - Ward, B.J., 2001-2005 (Box 22, Folder 53)
    - Watson, Ellen, 1998-2004 (Box 22, Folder 54)
    - Weir, Dara, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 55)
    - Weinstein, Norman (Box 22, Folder 56)
    - Weissbort, Daniel, 1989-2006 (Box 22, Folder 57)
    - Wickert, Max (Box 22, Folder 58)
    - Winner, Robert, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 59)
    - Witte, John, 1977-1987 (Box 22, Folder 60)
    - Wolff, Rebecca, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 61)
    - Wood, Susan, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 62)
    - Wylder, Deb, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 63)
    - Zisquit, Linda, 1986-2007 (Box 22, Folder 64)
    - Zulauf, Sander, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 65)
    - 2015 Addition, 1990-2012
      - A-B, 1997-2011 (Box 51, Folder 35)
      - A-B, 2007-2011 (Box 51, Folder 36)
      - C-D, 2007-2012 (Box 51, Folder 37)
      - E-F, 2007-2012 (Box 51, Folder 38)
      - G-H, 2007-2012 (Box 51, Folder 39)
      - I-L, 2007-2012 (Box 51, Folder 40)
      - M-P (Box 51, Folder 41)
      - Q-T, 2007-2012 (Box 51, Folder 42)
      - U-Z, 1990-2012 (Box 51, Folder 43)
  - Publishers and Editors, 1970-2005; 9.
    - American Poetry Review - Stephen Berg to G.S., 1974-2004 (Box 22, Folder 66)
    - American Poetry Review - G.S. to Stephen Berg, 1974-1977 (Box 22, Folder 67)
    - American Poetry Review - General, 1976-2003 (Box 22, Folder 68)
    - Boa Editions - A. Poulin, 1982-2000 (Box 22, Folder 69)
    - Cummington Press - Harry Duncan, 1970-1974 (Box 22, Folder 70)
    - Fiddlehead Poetry Books - Fred Cogswell, 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 71)
    - Harper & Row - Ted Solotaroff, 1983-1990 (Box 22, Folder 72)
    - Holy Cow Press - Jim Perlman, 1979-1981 (Box 22, Folder 73)
    - Houghton Mifflin Company - Johnathan Galassi, 1976-1985 (Box 22, Folder 74)
    - Houghton Mifflin Company - Thomas S. Hart, 1981-1983 (Box 22, Folder 75)
    - Houghton Mifflin Company - General, 1978-1992 (Box 22, Folder 76)
    - New Directions - James Laughlin, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 77)
    - New England Review, 1978-1992 (Box 22, Folder 78)
    - New Yorker - Howard Moss, 1976-1983 (Box 22, Folder 79)
    - New Yorker - General, 1983-1997 (Box 22, Folder 81)
    - Norton - Jill Bialosky, 1989-2000 (Box 22, Folder 82)
    - Norton - Carol Houck Smith, 1990-2005 (Box 22, Folder 83)
    - Norton - General, 1996-2004 (Box 22, Folder 84)
    - University Of Pittsburgh Press - Ed Ochester, 1977-1999 (Box 22, Folder 85)
    - University of Pittsburgh Press - General, 1978-2005 (Box 22, Folder 86)
    - W. Thomas Taylor, 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 87)
    - 2015 Addition, 2006-2012
      - Baker, David, 2009 (Box 51, Folder 44)
      - Bailosky, Jill, 2009-2012 (Box 51, Folder 45)
      - Bonano, David, 2008-2011 (Box 51, Folder 46)
      - Corey, Stephen, 2011-2012 (Box 51, Folder 47)
      - Epler, Barbara, 2008-2010 (Box 51, Folder 48)
      - Flinn, Mary, 2008-2010 (Box 51, Folder 49)
      - Fox, Curtis, 2011-2012 (Box 51, Folder 50)
      - Gorham, Sarah, 2006-2011 (Box 51, Folder 51)
      - Hougton Mifflin, 2009 (Box 51, Folder 52)
      - Koch, Hans, 2010 (Box 51, Folder 53)
      - Moss-Coane, Marty, 2009 (Box 51, Folder 54)
      - New Yorker, 2008-2010 (Box 51, Folder 55)
      - Quinn, Alice, 2008-2011 (Box 51, Folder 56)
      - Ras, Barbara, 2007-2012 (Box 51, Folder 57)
      - Simms, Michael, 2007-2010 (Box 51, Folder 58)
      - Simon, Daniel, 2009-2012 (Box 51, Folder 59)
      - Smith, Carol, 2006-2009 (Box 51, Folder 60)
      - Somerville, Jane, 2011 (Box 51, Folder 61)
      - Swenson, Tree, 2007-2012 (Box 51, Folder 62)
      - W.W. Norton, 2008-2012 (Box 51, Folder 63)
  - Critics, 1981-2005; 10.
    - Cheuse, Alan, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 88)
    - Kitchen, Judith (Box 22, Folder 89)
    - Lopate, Philip, 1991-1992 (Box 22, Folder 90)
    - Perloff, Marjorie, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 91)
    - Rossky, William (Box 22, Folder 92)
    - Somerville, Jane, 1981-2005 (Box 22, Folder 93)
  - Novelists and Prose Writers, 1980-2007; 11.
    - Bodanes, Jerome, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 94)
    - Conroy, Frank, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 95)
    - Frank, Joan, 2006 (Box 22, Folder 96)
    - Cornick, Vivian, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 97)
    - Havazelet, Ehud, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 98)
    - Hemple, Patricia (Box 22, Folder 99)
    - Petesch, Natalie, 1980-2002 (Box 22, Folder 100)
    - Shacochis, Robert, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 101)
    - West, Paul, 1983-1985 (Box 22, Folder 102)
    - Wolitzer, Hilma, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 103)
    - Zackheim, Michele, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 104)
    - 2015 Addition, 2007-2012
      - Aaron, Chester, 2010-2012 (Box 51, Folder 64)
      - Antoni, Robert, 2010-2012 (Box 51, Folder 65)
      - Bathanti, Joseph, 2007-2010 (Box 51, Folder 66)
      - Beeman, Robin, 2010-2011 (Box 51, Folder 67)
      - Canin, Ethan, 2009 (Box 51, Folder 68)
      - Clemente, Jennifer, 2008-2011 (Box 51, Folder 69)
      - Ehrenkrauz, Eleanor, 2011 (Box 51, Folder 70)
      - Freund, Diane, 2008-2011 (Box 51, Folder 71)
      - Goldworm, Irving, 2007-2012 (Box 51, Folder 72)
      - Hedges, Chris, 2007-2010 (Box 51, Folder 73)
      - Henley, Patricia, 2007-2011 (Box 51, Folder 74)
      - Hoffman, Aoina, 2007-2008 (Box 51, Folder 75)
      - Kinder, Chuck, 2008-2012 (Box 51, Folder 76)
      - Liebrecht, Savyon, 2008 (Box 51, Folder 77)
      - Lopate, Philip, 2012 (Box 51, Folder 78)
      - Oates, Joyce Carol, 2010-2011 (Box 51, Folder 79)
      - Rosenberg, David, 2012 (Box 51, Folder 80)
      - Schwartz, Lynne Sharon, 2011 (Box 51, Folder 81)
      - Smith, Nancy, 2008 (Box 51, Folder 82)
      - Taylor Hall, Mary Ann, 2003-2010 (Box 51, Folder 83)
      - Thomas, Abigail, 2006-2010 (Box 51, Folder 84)
      - Zackheim, Michelle (Box 51, Folder 85)
  - Artists, 1967-2007; 12.
    - Caracas-Rogovin, Gretchen (Box 22, Folder 105)
    - Fishman, Louise, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 106)
    - Herzberg, Victoria Shalvah and Don, 2006 (Box 22, Folder 107)
    - Major, Clarence, 2006 (Box 22, Folder 108)
    - Randall, Colleen, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 109)
    - Silbert, Layle, 1978-1993 (Box 22, Folder 110)
    - Stirner, Karl, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 111)
    - 2015 Addition, 1992-2012
      - Dobkin, Alix, 2010 (Box 51, Folder 86)
      - Feldstein, Peter, 2008-2010 (Box 51, Folder 87)
      - Fink, Larry (Box 51, Folder 88)
      - Fishman, Louise, 2009-2012 (Box 51, Folder 89)
      - Grubin, David & Joan, 2007-2012 (Box 51, Folder 90)
      - Hardwick, Cheryl, 2008-2009 (Box 51, Folder 91)
      - Haffka, Michael, 2011-2012 (Box 51, Folder 92)
      - Hillringhouse, Mark, 2007-2012 (Box 51, Folder 93)
      - Matthews, Paul, 1992-2012 (Box 51, Folder 94)
      - Posner, Martha, 2012 (Box 51, Folder 95)
      - Stirner, Karl, 2007-2012 (Box 51, Folder 96)
      - Yeros, Dimitros, 2011 (Box 51, Folder 97)
  - General, 1982-2002; 13.
    - Glenn Horowitz Bookseller, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 112)
    - Moyers, Bill, 1989-1994 (Box 22, Folder 113)
    - Ward, Christina, 1995-2002 (Box 22, Folder 114)
- Publicity, 1970-2007; V.
  This series contains publicity and advertising material from the early 1970s to 2007 and is arranged by date into three subseries.
  - 1970-1980 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - 1990-2000 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - 2000-2007 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Readings and Appointment Books, 1982-2012; VI.
  This series consists of Stern's personal files of letters and publicity about readings, including posters. Also included are appointment books which demonstrate his relentless public reading schedule. The series is arranged chronologically.
  New materials were added in 2015.
  - 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - 1985 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - 1986-1987 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - 1988 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - 1989 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - 1990 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - 1991 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - 1992 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - 1994 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - 1995 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - 1996 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - 2015 Addition, 1997-2012
    - Readings, 1997-2012; 1.
      - 1997 (Box 52, Folder 1-2)
      - 1998 (Box 52, Folder 3-4)
      - 1999 (Box 52, Folder 5-6)
      - 2000 (Box 52, Folder 7-9)
      - 2001 (Box 52, Folder 10-11)
      - 2002 (Box 52, Folder 12-13)
      - 2003 (Box 52, Folder 14-15)
      - 2004 (Box 52, Folder 16)
      - 2005 (Box 52, Folder 17-18)
      - 2006 (Box 52, Folder 19-20)
      - 2007 (Box 52, Folder 21-22)
      - 2008 (Box 53, Folder 1-3)
      - 2009 (Box 53, Folder 4-5)
      - 2010 (Box 53, Folder 6)
      - 2011 (Box 53, Folder 7-8)
      - 2012 (Box 53, Folder 9-10)
    - Appointment Books, 1997-2012; 2.
      - 1997 (Box 53, Folder 11)
      - 1998 (Box 53, Folder 12)
      - 1999 (Box 53, Folder 13)
      - 2000 (Box 53, Folder 14)
      - 2001 (Box 53, Folder 15)
      - 2001-2002 (Box 53, Folder 16)
      - 2003 (Box 53, Folder 17)
      - 2004 (Box 53, Folder 18)
      - 2005 (Box 53, Folder 19)
      - 2006 (Box 53, Folder 20)
      - 2007 (Box 53, Folder 21)
      - 2008 (Box 53, Folder 22)
      - 2009 (Box 53, Folder 23)
      - 2011 (Box 53, Folder 24)
      - 2012 (Box 53, Folder 25)
- General Activities, 1948-2005; VII.
  This series contains general poetry information and projects with which Stern has been involved and includes directories, articles, tapes, letters, talks, essays, political organizations, colleges, temporary college positions, prize judging, laureateships, radio appearances, etc. It is arranged in the order in which it was received.
  New material was added to this series in 2015 and is arranged alphabetically.
  - Bill Moyers, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - National Poetry Series, 1987-1991 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Israeli magazines, 1986-1987 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Books to buy, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - 1996 Geraldine R. Dodge Poetry Festival, 1988-1996 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - New York City Poets (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - New England Review, 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - California Institute of the Arts, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Speakers' Agency, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Squaw Valley, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Sarah Lawrence College, 1997-1999 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Spring Church Book Company, 1984-1996 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Poet Laureate, 2000-2001 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Radio, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Archives and papers, 1999-2005 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Prize judging, 1998-2001 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Proofreading marks (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Raritan Valley Community College, 1998-2004 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Friends of Peace Now, 1989-1990 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - New England College, 2004-2005 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - 1953 Crossroads, The Lake Grove School, Lake Grove N.Y. (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Religion, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Papers, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Gerald Stern Poetry Foundation, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Marianne Moore (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - MacArthur Foundation, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Loess Hills Books (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Judy Lubershane Agency, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Dodge Poets, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - University of Pittsburgh Honorary Degree, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Jewish Book Awards, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Conferences and readings, 1995-1999 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Joshua Beckman introduction (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Center for Book Arts, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Biographies of Gerald Stern, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Articles, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Art residencies, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Genealogy, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Gale Groups, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Directories, Flyers, Posters, etc., 1980-2003 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Guggenheim, 1975-2005 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Griffin Poetry Prize, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Artists' colonies, 1987-1992 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Critical essay, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Salary Recommendation Form, 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, 1983-1986 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - Sabbatical, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - Mileage Plus, 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Job offers, 1982-1989 (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - Lafayette College, 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - Course proposal (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - Independent study (Box 24, Folder 52)
  - MFA exam, 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 53)
  - Orpheus class, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 54)
  - Proposed fellowship, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 55)
  - International Writing Program, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 56)
  - Recommendations, 1981-1998 (Box 24, Folder 57)
  - Student recommendations, 1983-1993 (Box 24, Folder 58)
  - Letters of recommendation for Gerald Stern, 1979-1981 (Box 24, Folder 59)
  - Writing programs (Box 24, Folder 60)
  - Workshops, Fall 1982 (Box 24, Folder 61)
  - Fulbright Program, 1982-1984 (Box 24, Folder 62)
  - Jerry's Stew, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 63)
  - Alabama Chair, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 64)
  - Faculty Development Grant Application, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 65)
  - English Department Guidelines, 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 66)
  - Iowa course, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 67)
  - Haven, Steve, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 68)
  - Hikmit, 1948 (Box 24, Folder 69)
  - Green Haven Correctional Facility, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 70)
  - Hilai International, 1986-1987 (Box 24, Folder 71)
  - Holocaust, 1987-1988 (Box 24, Folder 72)
  - Moshe Dor (Box 24, Folder 73)
  - Iowa Governor's Institute, 1991-1994 (Box 24, Folder 74)
  - Djerassi Foundation, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 75)
  - Cole's Tape (Box 24, Folder 76)
  - Old resumes (Box 24, Folder 77)
  - Contests and prizes, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 78)
  - Contemporary American Poet-Critic, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 79)
  - Andover, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 80)
  - College of Santa Fe, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 81)
  - Cigna, 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 82)
  - Contemporary Authors, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 83)
  - Poetry Pilot, 1988-1989 (Box 24, Folder 84)
  - Pennsylvania Council on the Arts (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Poetry on Tape (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Visiting Poets Workshop (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Reconstructionist, 1987-1988 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Cranbrook Kingswood School, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Yiddish poets (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Yiddish, 1986-1988 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Jewish studies, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Workshop, 1990-1993 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Walt Whitman, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - New Jersey poets, 1976-1979 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Bennington, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Brittingham Prize, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Virginia Prize, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Readings, 1975-1981 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Walt Whitman International Poetry Center, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Poetry Resource Center, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Purdue, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - St. James Press, 1989-1990 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Addresses of publishers, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Credentials, 1947-1982 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Vitas (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Resumés (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Rejections from magazines (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Princeton evaluations, 1989-1990 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - "Guggy" recommendations (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Contemporary Poets, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Grants and fellowships awards, 1974-1982 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - 2015 Addition, 2003-2012
    - Academy of American Poets, Chancellorship Year's Correspondence, 2006-2008 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Academy of American Poets, Chancellorship Year's Correspondence, 2008-2011 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Academy of American Poets, Chancellorship Year's Correspondence, 2011 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Academy of American Poets' Wallace Stevens Award, 2006 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Addresses (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Adjunct Reader for Texas State, 2007-2008 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Amanda Bandler, 2009 (Box 54, Folder 7)